Lands are the foundation of your deck.
They provide all of the manna, or most of the manna that you use to cast spells to win.
These three cards are all forests, indicated by the forest at the top of the card.
The name of the card is forest, and that implies certain things about it.
This is an old revised edition of forest.
This is land halfway between the picture and the text box, and it has a t tilted and a colon, add one green manna to your manna pool.
This is a much more recent forest from the Lorwyn expansion set.
And it says basic land, dash forest which is like saying that it's a land with the name forest.
But it's much more specific.
As the sets have progressed, the way the cards are templated has become much more refined.
Instead of saying tap add one green to your manna pool, it only has the green manna symbol.
It's understood that this can be tapped to add a green manna to your manna pool.
This is far more simpler still.
It just says forest and has a picture that takes up nearly the entire forest, nearly the entire card.
All three of these cards are identical in terms of game play value.
The same would be true with any other of the five types.